I am Haruka Inoue, a 17-year-old high school sophomore from Kyoto, Japan.
I am Takako Inoue, a junior high school student, 14 years old, from Shizuoka Prefecture.
Please allow me to greet you.
I am Haruka Inoue, from Kyoto, a high school sophomore, 17 years old.
Please allow me to say hello.
I am Taiko Inoue, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
At this point, the most difficult part of this game is the most difficult part of this game.
The most difficult part of this game is the most difficult part of this game is the most difficult part of this game is the most difficult part of this game.
The most difficult part of this game is the most difficult part of this game is the most difficult part of this game is the most difficult part of this game is the most difficult part of this game
Groove's Queue
Thank you for watching!
I would like to introduce the 17th term members to you all.
Seventeenth term, come on!
Mae mae mae mae mae mae mae mae mae mae mae mae mae.
Please introduce yourself again.
I'm Haruka Mizukami, 17 years old, a high school sophomore, from Kyodo, Japan.
I am 17 years old and I look forward to working with you.
I am 14 years old and a junior high school student from Shizuoka, Japan.
I am 14 years old and a junior high school student.Best regards.
I will ask a lot of questions.
Yes, I will.
What do you think?
You can put a microphone on both of us. Mouth.
Yes.
Stick it.
I've got it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, then, let's continue.
I, Imijie Ahko's member color is,
Pure red.
Steky.
What would you like to be called by your fans?
I would like to be called Alsa.
Alsa
Kyoko.
How about you, Ako-chan?
I would like to be called Etta.
Really?
I was just messing around with it in rehearsal, but I really think that's what I'm going to be called.
Thank you very much to the two members of the team for coming.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
You there?
They're here.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Okay, watch this.
Bye-bye. Have fun after this.
I was just a customer.
Take care.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, man.
I'm nervous.
It's gonna be okay.
Let's go for it.
So, bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
What's up?
I'm nervous.
I can't believe I'm leaving now.
I'm in the place I'm in now.
I really don't
I would be a little irresponsible if I said I don't feel it.
I really can't believe it.
I really wanted to be here for a while.I really wanted him to be here for a while.
Today, he came to the section office with Chikopon,
Talk for a while.
Let me speak louder.
Someday I'll be introduced and I'll speak properly.
Yes, let's go.
Smile. Four more minutes and then the voice.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Let's go for it.
You think you can do it?
Yes, I'm fine.
Beautiful.
Loud and clear.
Okay, then,
Everyone, believe in what you have done for the past three months,
And new members, just do your best with a smile and a loud voice.
Let's be ourselves and have fun!
Yes, let's do our best!
Let's do our best!
I'm off!
Thank you for your hard work.
Mom, take some pictures as we go around there.
Wow!
What do you think?How do you feel about it?
No, I don't feel it yet.
I can hear the sound, but I don't feel it.
I'm a little anxious, but I'll keep smiling and do my best to stay positive.
I am 17-year-old Haga Inoue, a high school sophomore from Kyoto.
I'm Taiko Inoue, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
Well, trust that Haga's seniors will make it exciting.
Thank you for watching.
Good evening everyone gathered here at the Nippon Budokan.
This is Morning Musume。' 13.
Thank you very much.
I would like to introduce the 17th term members.
The 17th term, come here.
Come here.
Now, please introduce yourself.
Yes, I am Haruka Inoue.
I am Haruka Inoue, a 17-year-old high school sophomore from Kyoto Prefecture.
The difficult word I have recently learned is "transit production.
I look forward to working with you.
Cute!
I am Tomoko Inoue, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
My pride is my sharp radio calisthenics.
Oh!
You are sharp.
I like it.I like it.
Thank you very much.
We are both very nervous.
So, please support Morning Musume。 Please support Morning Musume's 23, which will have 14 members.
So, thank you very much to the two members of the 17th term.
Bye bye!
Please watch us.
Thank you. Hugs Sackett, take care.
Come on in Two!
Come here!
Ichi Daimyo, Ikuta Erina
Maizuki Fukuda
Sakira Miki
Haruka Yamamoto
Thanks a lot!
It was Marius Entry!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much for your hard work.
I was very nervous before I went on stage,
But when I got on stage, I saw so many open nights for the first time,
I was very moved and I was able to relax a bit and enjoy the show.
Especially during the encore,
I could see the audience's faces clearly for the first time,For the first time, I could clearly see the faces of the audience,
I was very moved, and it made me want to do my best from now on,
I will never forget that feeling and will continue to do my best.
I was very surprised that the penlights turned mint green so quickly,
I was very surprised and happy because it was dyed in an instant.
I knew from my senpai that they would change the penlights,
I knew from my seniors that they would change the penlights, but when they did, I was very excited to see them do it for real.
My nickname is Kasuga-san,
It was a little strange because my name is followed by "san," but I was very happy to be called by everyone,
I was very happy to be called by everyone.
I have never been called "getter" at school, so I was very happy to be called by everyone,
It was the first time for me to be called by someone else,
I was called by everyone, and it made me feel more prepared to live my life as a getter from now on.
I am sure that the time to perform with them will come in no time,
I think I will be able to perform with them in no time.
I hope to give a strong performance so that I can mix with them.
I want to practice more and more so that my performance will be powerful
I would like to practice more and more so that I can be a part of them.
I will never forget the excitement I felt today.
I will never forget this feeling I had today.
lessons and rehearsals
I will do my best in all of them.